[Applause]
welcome everybody to the 2017 yu-gi-oh
Championship
I am your announcer for tonight my name
is Richard and this my homeboy from the
hood should man how's it hangin who's
ready to watch some card games you know
I am black boy just don't steal
anybody's carts when I not look in their
security guard by the door and they're
watching your ass looks like the crowd
is getting pretty anxious
Jarro it looks like it I guess we
shouldn't keep them waiting any longer
it's time to do Oh I can't believe
this
who would have guessed Sonic the
Hedgehog would face his bro I'll go
first
is that alright with you bro fine by me
only noobs need to go first haha damn
he's already talking and the duel
hasn't even begun let's just hope that
doesn't come back to bite him and his
smelly ass time to begin I draw one card
well bro it looks like this duel is over
what's this sauna claims to be planning
something I play the spell card dark
magic curtain by paying half of my life
points I get to summon the Dark Magician
from my deck then I'll play two cards
facedown and end my turn
damn he isn't giving any mercy he
cornered Manic like a what
can he possibly do now I don't get it
why did Sonic give up half of his life
points to just to play one card are you
serious right now you dumb that
isn't just some card that's the
dark magician that is the
greatest card in his entire deck half of
your life points is nothing when you get
your aids card onto the field all we can
do now is hope that mana can pull
something out of his ass
so Andre what do you think Manik will do
to counter this honestly Richard I think
that boys done I mean look at
the look on his face
he'll probably surrender or something
they're right maybe I should just
surrender
no I can't give up not with all of these
people believing in me
I draw
[Music]
perfect I grew everything I need to turn
this duel around with the spell card
polymerization I can fuse two of my
monsters impressive row however he's
still no match for my Dark Magician
[Music]
I'm not finished yet I play the field
spell skyscraper
when's ty scraper is on the field all of
my elemental heroes get another 1000
attack points
oh he actually did it going on
Manic his ass kick his ass go
Elemental Hero flame wingman attack his
dark magician too bad medic you just
activated my trap with magic cylinder
you take battle damage equal to your
monsters at hack instead oh no run Manic
there is no running promise hang in
there medic we still believe in you wow
this Manic kid is no I don't
think he is Johnson look at him the
determination in his eyes
[Music]
[Applause]
this is this is simply incredible never
have I seen children duel with such
passion yet I believe these two boys
just grabbed how to breed this duel of
all time it's a shame that both of these
boys can't be winners only one can win
the grand prize of $50 that's right
but it's not about the prize
money anymore though it's about their
pride yes their pride as a duelist Sonic
Manic show them show all these
what you're capable of
[Applause]
[Music]
you
Oh
this is boring as I can't believe
we drove all the way down here just to
watch a card game Elena
hoo-ee caters like what we care
bearish
teimi say we spent so met Intel over
yoga vetto putit bow in folk interior
office
we can't Yoba morale came in do portray
you here
kick his ass Manic baby including for
you cause I'm not a your
route
youch excuse me you two in the stands
can you keep it down please sorry about
that my brother was just being a whiny
but it looks like this will be mannix
final turn I wonder what he will do they
are right this may be my final turn I
have no cards left in my hand
Sonic however has 5 on top of that he
has 3 monsters while I have none he also
has two facedown cards there is only one
card in my deck that can save my ass if
I don't draw it here I look
I end my turn oh dear God
did he not draw
card he needed well my own bro I guess
it's time I make the final move
I draw
I play the spell card monster reborn
monster reborn the card that lets you
bring back any monster that was
destroyed during the duel exactly and
the monster I chooses your flame wingman
look everyone Sonic just summoned mannix
ace card unto his own field could this
be the end go on flame wingman why don't
you give my bro a taste of his own
medicine
[Music]
you too sure gave a wonderful duel now
to give you your prizes for you Manic
this medal you didn't win but take it
anyway as a consolation prize go ahead
and put it on so everyone can see
[Laughter]
and now for you Sonic you get the grand
prize of $50 Timothy bring this boy his
prize money I regret to inform you that
the prize money L disappeared sir
what you can't be serious we are sir and
that's not all the black man is missing
as well
everyone hurry up and catch the black
man whoever catches him first gets half
of the money
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]